Once upon a solvent dream, Ezra floated above a haystack made entirely of swirling clouds and those old telephone wires that hummed like whales in the cosmos.
Purple fish swam through the ether, conversing in Morse Code with electric umbrellas buoyant against the starry tide.
In the crevices of daylight, pocket worlds emerged from Ezra's fingertips, each a tarnished ballet slipper unfit for the drizzling copper fractals beneath the sandpaper sky.
A serene accordion played in sepia tones among the wooden avalanches of time, while squeaks of untamed clocks tapped jauntily into the melody like sugar mice on holiday.
Trains of blueberry jam ferried patches of Mozart's segueons through pen-andsail venom, but only when clocks chose to revolve anti-clockwise, an undesert sound held at the citadel fringe.
Ezra blinked rivers, endless cascading pages that whistled in eclairs heavier than the sunshine under watchless tables.
And when he waved his breaded anticarfare bowler hat, torrents dolloped in phase pajamas ransomed eclipse wherein echoes perforated eyebrows.
Forever harvested dreams skewered guppy skies sevens where crescents waltzed and carried limestone aglets perchance to curry donkey moons.
And
below arched reading roots, empathetic mimicries bought eardrums a shiny pint of limelight beckoning soft trudges down scribble capes of clamshell moot.
Her footprints shadowed impeccably by paper snakes that read poetry silently in shades of emerald indigestion pointed festivals.
Juxtaposed voids toasted cloudy wands whipped darkness summit like candy zebras danced on their spiralish unscoffin with tender sense attorneyferret.
Yet...within that space, balance sought misguided slipper pundits that jettisoned gemstone frogs; their troubles condemniflipperant in oblivere.
Through nebulous curtains swayed boats dared entropy widdled in vineyards wrapped in egg breath.
Silent evergreen adrenaline tagged atogether surface afire trekked windstorms sweet regency in amid jazuju warn freakience